(Amy:)before he shut down.
(Amy:)Whenever I see
a bucket of dirty water,
I still hear "Lady in Red."
(Bernadette:)My prom was pretty
terrible, too.
(Bernadette:)I was so excited
about my date,
(Bernadette:)but it turned out
he only asked me
(Bernadette:)'cause he liked my friend.
(Bernadette:)He spent the whole night
talking about her.
(Amy:)Okay, we get it, you had
a friend and a date.
(Amy:)Stop bragging.
(Penny:)Doesn't matter.
(Penny:)Prom is silly anyways.
(Bernadette:)Easy for you to say;
you probably went
(Bernadette:)with the captain
of the football team.
(scoffs)
No.
(Penny:)I just made out
with him a little
(Penny:)while his date was puking.
(Amy:)My date would've had
to clean that up.
(Bernadette:)Ooh, I have an idea.
(Bernadette:)Maybe we can have,
like, a prom do-over.
(Amy:)Oh, that would be so much fun.
(Amy:)We could decorate the roof
and make the guys wear tuxedos.
(Bernadette:)Ooh, and get our hair done,
and slow-dance.
(Penny:)Okay, guys, trust me,
(Penny:)as someone who's been to,
like, seven proms,
(Penny:)it is never as good
as you want it to be.
(Amy:)You went to seven proms?
(Penny:)Yeah, let's see.